Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - COMMITTEE, COMMISSION, SECTION AND INTEREST GROUP RECORDS, 1922-1980; SERIES VII (Box-folder 2/28-4/28, 20/38-23/41, 31/23-32/13, 42/15-44/27, 54/9-57/11, 65/9-67/18, 72/6-72/32)
    - Head Nurse Section history, 1955-1958 (Box-folder 43/13)
    - Head Nurse Section Executive Committee, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 43/14)
    - Head Nurse Section Economic Security Committee, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 43/15)
    - Head Nurse Section Committee on Nominations, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 43/16)
    - Head Nurse Section Committee on Practice, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 43/17)
    - Committee to Plan Head Nurse Conference, 1964 (Box-folder 43/18)
    - Joint Committee on Employment Standards (part 1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 43/19)
    - Joint Committee on Employment Standards (part 2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 43/20)
    - Joint Committee on Employment Standards (part 1 of 3), 1966 (Box-folder 43/21)
    - Joint Committee on Employment Standards (part 2 of 3), 1966 (Box-folder 43/22)
    - Joint Committee on Employment Standards (part 3 of 3), 1966 (Box-folder 43/23)
    - Joint Section Committee meetings, 1955-1964 (Box-folder 43/24)
    - Joint Section Committee meetings, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 43/25)
    - Committee on Nominations, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 43/26)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section Executive Committee (part 1 of 2), 1959-1966 (Box-folder 43/27)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section Executive Committee (part 2 of 2), 1959-1966 (Box-folder 43/28)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section Executive Committee, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 43/29)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section Economic Security Committee, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 43/30)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section Committee on Nominations, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 43/31)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section Committee on Practice, 1955-1967 (Box-folder 43/32)
    - Office Nurse Section Executive Committee, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 43/33)
    - Office Nurse Section - medical assistants correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 43/34)
    - Office Nurse Section Economic Security Committee, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 43/35)
    - Office Nurse Section Committee on Nominations, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 43/36)
    - Office Nurse Section Committee on Practice, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 43/37)
    - Private Duty Section Executive Committee, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 43/38)
    - Private Duty Section Executive Committee, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 43/39)
    - Private Duty Section Economic Security Committee, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 43/40)
    - Private Duty Section Committee on Practice, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - Private Duty Section resources, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - Committee on Professional Nursing Practice correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Committee on Professional Nursing Practice correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Public Health Section history, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - Public Health Section history, 1949-1964 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Public Health Section Executive Committee minutes, 1947-1957 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - Public Health Section Executive Committee, 1951-1962 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - Public Health Section Executive Committee, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 44/9)
    - Public Health Section Economic Security Committee, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - Public Health Section Committee on Nominations, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - Public Health Section officer nominations, 1965 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - Public Health Section joint meeting on job classifications, 1965 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - Public Health Section Committee on Practice, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Public Health Section Program Committee, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Public Health Section Occupational Health Executive Committee, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 44/16)
    - Public Health Section Occupational Health correspondence, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - Public Health Section School Nurses Branch (part 1 of 2), 1954-1964 (Box-folder 44/18)
    - Public Health Section School Nurses Branch (part 2 of 2), 1954-1964 (Box-folder 44/19)
    - Public Health Section School Nurses Branch, 1957-1966 (Box-folder 44/20)
    - Committee on Public Relations, 1964 (Box-folder 44/21)
    - Registry Committee, District 3 Pierce County, 1953-1962 (Box-folder 44/22)
    - Registry Committee, District 3 Pierce County reports, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 44/23)
    - Registry Committee, District 4 Inland Empire, 1954-1964 (Box-folder 44/24)
    - Registry Committee, District 4 Inland Empire reports, 1953-1964 (Box-folder 44/25)
    - Registry Committee studies, 1958 (Box-folder 44/26)
    - Nurses Clinical Conference Committee, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 44/27)
    - Advisory Council, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 54/9)
    - Bylaws Committee, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 54/10)
    - Careers Committee: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 54/11)
    - Careers Committee: minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 54/12)
    - Clinical Conference Committee: minutes, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 54/13)
    - Committee on Committees: correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 54/14)
    - Committee on Committees: minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 54/15)
    - Committee on Committees: appointments, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 54/16)
    - Committee on Committees: recommendations, 1970 (Box-folder 54/17)
    - Committee on Committees: recommendations, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 54/18)
    - Committee on Committees: alternate list of appointments, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 54/19)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 54/20)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 54/21)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 54/22)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: minutes and reports, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 54/23)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: minutes and reports, 1970 (Box-folder 54/24)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 54/25)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 54/26)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 54/27)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice Subcommittee on Continuing Education, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 54/28)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Continuing Education (part 1 of 2), 1972 (Box-folder 54/29)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Continuing Education (part 2 of 2), 1972 (Box-folder 54/30)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Continuing Education (part 1 of 2), 1973 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Continuing Education (part 2 of 2), 1973 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Continuing Education: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Subcommittee on Legal, Ethical and Professional Standards: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Subcommittee on Legal, Ethical and Professional Standards: minutes and reports, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Subcommittee on Legal, Ethical and Professional Standards: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Luncheon Program Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Nurse Preparation and Utilization: correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Nurse Preparation and Utilization: correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Nurse Preparation and Utilization: minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Nurse Preparation and Utilization: minutes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 55/11)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Nurse Preparation and Utilization: resources, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/12)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Special Committee on Nursing Education, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 55/13)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Committee on Nursing Service Administrators, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 55/14)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Commission on Economic and General Welfare Liaison Committee, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/15)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Commission on Economic and General Welfare Liaison Committee: minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 55/16)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Ad Hoc Committee Develop Camp Nursing Standards, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/17)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Inservice Education Planning Committee: correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/18)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice -- Inservice Education Planning Committee: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/19)
    - Committee on Common Interests and Goals, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/20)
    - Committee on Common Interests and Goals: minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/21)
    - Committee on Cooperation, 1972 (Box-folder 55/22)
    - Convention Local Arrangements Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/23)
    - Convention Planning Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/24)
    - Convention Program Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 55/25)
    - Convention Resolutions Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/26)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 55/27)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 55/28)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 55/29)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: convention program, 1972 (Box-folder 55/30)
    - Finance Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 55/31)
    - Geriatric Interest Group, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 55/32)
    - Geriatric Interest Group, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/33)
    - Geriatric Interest Group: correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 55/34)
    - Geriatric Interest Group: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/35)
    - Headquarters Personnel Committee, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Headquarters Personnel Committee, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Inservice Education Interest Group: correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Inservice Education Interest Group Steering Committee, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Inservice Education Interest Group: minutes, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Inter-organizational Relationships Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Joint Practices Commission: correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Joint Practices Commission: minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Legislation Committee: correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Legislation Committee: correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Legislation Committee: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Legislation Committee: minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 56/12)
    - Legislation Committee: statements, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 56/13)
    - Membership Promotion Committee: correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 56/14)
    - Membership Promotion Committee: correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 56/15)
    - Membership Promotion Committee: minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 56/16)
    - Minority Committee: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 56/17)
    - Minority Committee: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 56/18)
    - Minority Committee: survey, 1971 (Box-folder 56/19)
    - Nominations Committee (part 1 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 56/20)
    - Nominations Committee (part 2 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 56/21)
    - Nominations Committee: minutes, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 56/22)
    - Nominations Committee: resources, 1971 (Box-folder 56/23)
    - Nominations Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 56/24)
    - Nominations Committee: resources, 1973 (Box-folder 56/25)
    - Special Committee of Nursing Service Administrators, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 56/26)
    - Committee to Plan President's Forum, 1969 (Box-folder 56/27)
    - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner/Associate Interest Group, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 56/28)
    - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner/Associate Interest Group: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 56/29)
    - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner/Associate Interest Group: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 56/30)
    - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner/Associate Interest Group: resources, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 56/31)
    - Platform Committee, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Private Duty Nurses Ad hoc Committee, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Ad hoc Committee for Public Health Nurses (part 1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Ad hoc Committee for Public Health Nurses (part 2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Scholarships and Loans Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Task Force Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Washington State Physician - Professional Nurse Liaison Committee, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Tri-organization Special Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - Ad hoc Task Force on Continuing Health Education Coordination, 1973 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: minutes, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: evaluation of models, 1979-. (Box-folder 65/13)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: resources (part 1 of 3), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 65/14)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: resources (part 2 of 3), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 65/15)
    - American Nurses' Association Committee to Study Roles and Functions: resources (part 3 of 3), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 65/16)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 65/17)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 65/18)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 65/19)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 65/20)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: correspondence, 1979 (Box-folder 65/21)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: minutes, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 65/22)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: Ad hoc Committee to Study Public Health Nursing Job Classifications, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 65/23)
    - Commission on Economic and General Welfare: Subcommittee to Write Behavioral Objectives, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 65/24)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice (part 1 of 3), 1974 (Box-folder 65/25)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice (part 2 of 3), 1974 (Box-folder 65/26)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice (part 3 of 3), 1974 (Box-folder 65/27)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 65/28)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1977 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1977 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Commission on Nursing Practice: resource file, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Committee to Study Revisions in Nurse Practice Act, 1971 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Advisory Council: minutes, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Bylaws Committee, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Bylaws Committee: correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Bylaws Committee: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Committee on Committees, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - Committee on Committees, 1974 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - Committee on Committees: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - Common Interests and Goals Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 66/15)
    - Continuing Education Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - Continuing Education Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 66/17)
    - Continuing Education Committee, 1976 (Box-folder 66/18)
    - Committee on Continuing Education Recognition Program: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 66/19)
    - Convention Planning Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 66/20)
    - Finance Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 66/21)
    - Finance Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 66/22)
    - Headquarters Personnel Committee, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 66/23)
    - Legislation Committee: correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 66/24)
    - Legislation Committee: correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 66/25)
    - Legislation Committee: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 66/26)
    - Legislation Committee: manuals and bulletins, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 66/27)
    - Membership Promotion Committee (part 1 of 2), 1973 (Box-folder 66/28)
    - Membership Promotion Committee (part 2 of 2), 1973 (Box-folder 66/29)
    - Membership Promotion Committee, 1974 (Box-folder 66/30)
    - Minority Affairs Committee: correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 66/31)
    - Minority Affairs Committee: correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 66/32)
    - Minority Affairs Committee: correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 66/33)
    - Minority Affairs Committee: correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 66/34)
    - Minority Affairs Committee: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 66/35)
    - Nominating Committee: correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 66/36)
    - Nominating Committee: correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 66/37)
    - Nominating Committee: minutes, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Platform Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Public Health Nursing Standing Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Resolutions Committee, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Consumer Relations Task Force: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Consumer Relations Task Force: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Geriatric Interest Group: correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Geriatric Interest Group: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - IV Nurses Interest Group, 1974 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Inservice Education Interest Group, 1974 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Nurse Practitioner Interest Group: correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - Nurse Practitioner Interest Group: minutes, 1975 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner / Associate Interest Group: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - Joint Practices Commission: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/14)
    - Joint Practices Commission: minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 67/15)
    - Women's Health Care Interest Group, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 67/16)
    - Women's Health Care Interest Group Task Force on Continuing Education, 1975 (Box-folder 67/17)
    - Women's Health Care Interest Group Task Force on Scope of Nursing Practice, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 67/18)
    - Advisory Council, 1958-1968 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers Section (part 1 of 2), 1961-1970 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers Section (part 2 of 2), 1961-1970 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - General Duty Section (part 1 of 2), 1959-1970 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - General Duty Section (part 2 of 2), 1959-1970 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - Head Nurse Section, 1959-1970 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section (part 1 of 2), 1951-1970 (Box-folder 72/12)
    - Nursing Service Administrators Section (part 2 of 2), 1951-1970 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - Office Nurse Section (part 1 of 2), 1951-1970 (Box-folder 72/14)
    - Office Nurse Section (part 2 of 2), 1951-1970 (Box-folder 72/15)
    - Office Nurse Section -- committees, 1954-1967 (Box-folder 72/16)
    - Private Duty Section (part 1 of 2), 1951-1970 (Box-folder 72/17)
    - Private Duty Section (part 2 of 2), 1951-1970 (Box-folder 72/18)
    - Private Duty Section rules and regulations, 1922 (Box-folder 72/19)
    - Public Health Nurses Section (part 1 of 3), 1958-1970 (Box-folder 72/20)
    - Public Health Nurses Section (part 2 of 3), 1958-1970 (Box-folder 72/21)
    - Public Health Nurses Section (part 3 of 3), 1958-1970 (Box-folder 72/22)
    - Public Health Nurses Section -- Economic Security Committee, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 72/23)
    - Public Health Nurses Section -- School Nurse Branch, 1954-1964 (Box-folder 72/24)
    - Public Health Nurses Section -- Committee on Employment Standards (part 1 of 2), 1956-1962 (Box-folder 72/25)
    - Public Health Nurses Section -- Committee on Employment Standards (part 2 of 2), 1956-1962 (Box-folder 72/26)
    - Public Health Nurses Section -- Committee on Employment Standards (part 3 of 2), 1956-1962 (Box-folder 72/27)
    - Committee on Committees, 1952 (Box-folder 72/28)
    - Legislative Committee (part 1 of 2), 1962-1969 (Box-folder 72/29)
    - Legislative Committee (part 2 of 2), 1962-1969 (Box-folder 72/30)
    - Nursing Information Bureau, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 72/31)
    - Washington State League of Nursing - Washington State Nurses Association Coordinating Council, 1958-1963 (Box-folder 72/32)
  - ECONOMIC SECURITY PROGRAM RECORDS, SERIES VIII
    - NEGOTIATION AND AGREEMENT RECORDS, 1943-1975; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 4/29-6/20, 23/42, 32/14-32/31, 44/28-46/49, 57/12-57/17, 67/19-67/22)
      - Boeing nurses history, 1945-1954 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - Boeing Airplane Company: NLRB petition, etc., 1948-1949 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - Boeing Company (part 1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 4/31)
      - Boeing Company (part 2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 4/32)
      - Cowlitz General Hospital, Longview (part 1 of 2), 1955-1966 (Box-folder 4/33)
      - Cowlitz General Hospital, Longview (part 2 of 2), 1955-1966 (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Ellensburg General Hospital, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 4/35)
      - Firland Sanatorium, Seattle, 1950-1964 (Box-folder 4/36)
      - General Electric Company, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 4/37)
      - Grays Harbor Community Hospital, Aberdeen, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 4/38)
      - Group Health Cooperative (part 1 of 2), 1948-1964 (Box-folder 4/39)
      - Group Health Cooperative (part 2 of 2), 1948-1964 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - Group Health Cooperative, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 4/41)
      - Harrison Memorial Hospital, Bremerton, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - King County Hospital (Harborview) (part 1 of 2), 1948-1966 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - King County Hospital (Harborview) (part 2 of 2), 1948-1966 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Mountain View General Hospital, Tacoma, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 23/42)
      - Omak Memorial Hospital, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Northern Pacific Railway Company stewardess-nurses, 1963 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Northwest Hospital Council, 1958-1962 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Northwest Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Northwest Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Northwest Hospital Council, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 67/19)
      - Northwest Hospital Council, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 67/20)
      - Northwest Hospital Council, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 67/21)
      - Olympic Memorial Hospital, Port Angeles (part 1 of 2), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Olympic Memorial Hospital, Port Angeles (part 2 of 2), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - Olympic Memorial Hospital, Port Angeles (part 1 of 2), 1952-1965 (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Olympic Memorial Hospital, Port Angeles (part 2 of 2), 1952-1965 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Our Lady of Lourdes Hospital, Pasco (part 1 of 2), 1955-1960 (Box-folder 5/13)